http://www.ninyoandmoore.com/privacy/

Ninyo & Moore Geotechnical and Environmental Sciences Consultants.
Ninyo & Moore provides geotechnical engineering, engineering geology, geophysics, hydrogeology, soil and materials testing, and environmental services.
3202 East Harbour Drive
Phoenix,
AZ
Phone: 602.243.1600
Geotechnical & Environmental Sciences Consultants
Geotechnical & Environmental Sciences Consultants
LinkedIn
Twitter
Facebook
800.427.0401
HomeAbout UsServicesQualificationsCareersLocationsContact UsLogin
Home  >  Privacy
Privacy
Ninyo & Moore is committed to treating our clients, employees and partners with respect. This privacy policy reiterates this commitment. Ninyo & Moore operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems to aid in our commitment.
Ninyo & Moore collects no personally identifying information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly requested (such as voluntary submission of an e-mail address in the Contact Us form). Ninyo & Moore will not trade, sell, or rent personal information. If you send us e-mail with questions, comments or your resume, you should know that e-mail is not necessarily secure against interception. We will use and store the personal information that you provide (e.g., your e-mail address, name, address) only to respond to your message as appropriate. Only authorized employees have access to the information you provide.
Our web servers may seek to place a “cookie” on your computer’s hard drive which allows the server to determine the computer when it visits again. Ninyo & Moore uses the data to perform statistical analyses and to measure overall user demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the site. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data, and the information that is tracked is only used for internal purposes. However, if you prefer not to accept cookies, you can set your browser to reject them or to alert you before one is placed.
We reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy at any time. Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes.
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page.
Navigation
HomeAbout UsServicesQualificationsCareersLocationsContact UsLogin
Copyright © 2020 Ninyo & Moore.All rights reserved.
